So, I recently did a trading challenge
where I gave Claude $10,000 of my real
money to trade stocks. And at the end of
the month, I was actually beating the
S&P by a little over 8%, which I was
pretty impressed by. And now that GBT6
Astra is out and it's even more
powerful, I'm going to do the exact same
thing. So, before I kick off that
$10,000 challenge, I wanted to actually
just show you guys how I'm getting this
all set up so that you can replicate
this if you want to turn Astra into a
24/7 trader for you. So, let's not waste
any time and just get straight into this
one. All right, so before we get
started, I just want to say this is not
financial advice. I'm not recommending
you give an agent $10,000 to trade. I'm
recommending that maybe you start with
paper trading, you get a strategy that
you like, and then you automate some of
that. Or if you're already consistently
trading every day and every week, then
maybe just see if you can use AI to help
you get more updates or to help you keep
an eye on things so that you're not
having to like pocket watch different
stocks or something like that. But
anyways, let's just jump in here and let
me show you how simple this is to set
up. So right here where I'm at is I'm
about to set up all of the automatic
routines so that this thing can run
without me. So, I wanted to show you
guys, I asked right now in as simple
terms as possible, explain our strategy
and what we're going to do. So, here's
what Astra came back with. We built the
strategy around three constraints.
$10,000, seven trading days, and we're
doing six wakeups or six checks per day.
So, what I started off with was I
literally was just having a conversation
with Astra. I was saying, "Hey, I have
this challenge. I want to take, you
know, a new strategy, so it's a little
bit more risky. I have seven days to try
to make money." And I asked it to just
do a bunch of research. So, it fanned
out like 10 sub agents, and it
researched a ton of stuff. As you can
see, we've got this big dock where we
talk about the strategy and it
consolidated a bunch of research
information. Now, this is where I see
there being sort of two paths. You have
the path where you don't really have a
trading strategy and you're wanting to
sort of outsource that research and
thinking to AI agents or you've got the
path where you are consistently trading
every day and you want to just help
yourself be able to move faster or not,
you know, forget things. So, in this
case, what I did is I wanted to
outsource that thinking and I wanted to
have Astra come up with a strategy. I'm
basically just helping guide it. And
what it came up with is this schedule.
So 7:45 a.m. Central, we're going to
read the news, check the account, and
choose stocks to watch. So, let me just
pull up a little calendar here to show
you guys what that actually looks like.
Here's the first time that Ash is going
to wake up on trading days about 7:45,
and it's going to read the news, check
the account, and choose what stocks to
watch. Now, this is where I would say if
you are someone who's consistently
trading, think about your day like this,
you know, market open, market close,
what do you do? Maybe before the market
opens, do you look at some stuff? Maybe
an hour in, do you look at some stuff?
you know, maybe before close, do you
look at some stuff? And just sort of put
yourself on this like 1-day calendar
because then you can just basically make
agents to do those things at those times
to help you out a little bit. But
anyways, let me just keep going here
with the proposed plan from Codeex. At
9:30 a.m., it's going to look for the
first qualifying trade. So now we have
agent wake up number two. At 11:00 a.m.,
it's going to review positions and
consider the last new trade. At 1 p.m.,
it's going to manage existing positions.
At 2:15, we're going to close out the
remaining positions. And so it's kind of
taking more of a day trading strategy
rather than a long-term trading
strategy. And then at 245, right before
a close, it's going to confirm we're out
and record the day results. So that's
how simple this is going to be. Every
single trading day, it's going to do
these actions at these times. And that's
how we're going to basically make this
24/7 trader for our 7-day challenge.
Now, if you'd feel more comfortable
having another wake up after the market
closes, you can do that. Or if you want
another one before the market opens, you
can do that as well. This is just what
Astra came up with for this specific
challenge. Now, the important piece that
I wanted to call out here is about
continuity. Meaning, every single time
that one of these agents wakes up, it's
stateless. And so, what we have to make
sure it does is that it reads through
the project, it looks at our portfolio,
and it understands what it needs to do.
It understands the context of what just
happened in order to understand better
what I need to do now. And so, the way
that I'm kind of tackling this here is
having every single wakeup end with a
progress log. So, that way we have
basically this system where, you know,
one agent wakes up and starts working.
It will basically say, you know, here's
what I did today and here's what comes
next. So then when this next agent wakes
up and basically takes over, it will
read that output. It will do its work
and then go, okay, cool. Here's what I
just did. And then we just basically
have this loop where every single time
the next agent wakes up, it's able to
take over all the work. It's able to
orient itself with what's going on and
just keep actually feeling like it's one
trading agent rather than having a bunch
of different isolated workers. So you
can see here it says continuity comes
from shared records, not the AI
remembering the conversation. So every
wakeup will read the strategy and the
previous handoff, check Alpaca, which is
where we're trading. I'll show you guys
that in a sec to see what actually
happened, perform its assigned job,
update the current account state and
progress log, and then leave clear
instructions for the next wake up. And
if you don't have this continuity, it's
just going to feel like you're just kind
of like throwing darts at the wall.
Critical actions get recorded as they
happen, so an interrupted run can be
recovered without accidentally repeating
a trade. So all of this stuff is ready
and now we just have to actually set up
the connection to Alpaca and set up the
actual routines. And setting up the
routines is important. So I will talk
about that when we get there. But I did
real quick want to show you guys some
stuff in this doc. So here are the
persistent files. The ones I wanted to
call out are the progress log. You can
see here's everything that's going to
happen. We have an actual journal as
well which can be appended and we have
evidence. Now I also brainstorm with
Astra on some failures. So failure
behavior would be no previous progress
record on the first run. Next model has
no chat history. prior run crashed after
sending an order, two runs overlap,
missing or corrupt, or the machine or
app go offline. And by the way, guys, to
make this easier, I did put all of this
into a free resource guide so that you
can basically give this to an agent if
you want to help it sort of set up the
same sort of system that we have here.
And you can get this for completely free
by joining my free school community. The
link for that is down in the
description. You'll come in here, you'll
go to classroom and click on all YouTube
resources, and everything will be in
there. And you'll find the doc
associated with this video and all of my
other skills and repos and things like
that. So, if you want that doc, go ahead
and grab it. But let's get back to the
video. So, next up here is we need to go
to Alpaca to get the actual connection
set up. So, here is my Alpaca account.
You can see that if you make an account
here, you can also have a paper trading
account. So, you could get on here and
connect your agent to this and just have
it trade for you for, you know, a couple
months or a couple weeks or however long
it takes for you to feel comfortable
with the strategy. And then you can move
it over to real money. But this is just
paper trading. So, it's going to follow
the market. It's real stocks, but it's
fake money. So, you can paper trade
first and then you can open up an actual
brokerage account here. And this is
$10,000 of real cash in this account.
Now, so if you want to actually follow
along with this sort of video, then
you're going to want to go get an alpaca
account set up. So you can grab the API
key and put it into your codeex. You can
see right here there's API keys. It
gives you this endpoint. And then we
have the actual key right here. So what
I'm going to do is I'm going to copy
this key. And obviously this is like a
password to your trading account. So
don't give this key to anybody. Also,
don't put this key into the chat window
of CEX. I'm going to show you where you
put this. What you're going to do is
you're going to ask it to create you
aenv file or if you're already in your
AOS or if you're already in a project
that has one, you're going to put it in
there. Now, what I did specifically is I
put this trading challenge inside of my
AIOS. So, if I open up these files, you
can see this is what my project for this
trading challenge looks like. We have
our docs, we have our agents.mmd. We
even have a cloud. MD if we want to move
it over. We have scripts, routines, we
have ourv, but this actually lives
within my HERK 2. So, it's in my Herk 2.
It's in a folder called other worlds,
which is where I have a bunch of other
worlds. And then we have our Astra
trading bot challenge. So, I'm going to
be running the routines in this project
just so I can keep everything sort of
like isolated, and I don't want too much
context polluting the window. I don't
want confusion or bloat to get into my
trading bot because all my trading bot
has to think about or look at is trading
information. It doesn't need to know
about my business or my projects. But, I
do want my overall herk 2 to be able to
have better visibility into the trading
challenge just for context. So, that's
how I'm isolating this project. So
anyways, what I'm going to do is I need
to open up my files over here and I need
to put my alpaca API key that you guys
just saw me copy. I need to put that
into theenv. I'm going to go to the
Astra trading challenge and I'm going to
open up theenv and I'm going to paste it
right in here. Now, when you do this
with real money, you're going to have to
click on regenerate because that will
give you an API key and an alpaca
secret. And you do need both of those
things. So you'll copy the key and then
you'll put that in the right spot in
here. You can see right here, a alpaca
API key. And now you can see that I've
pasted in my API key as well as my
secret. And I save that. And now we want
to check if Codex can actually look into
that account. All right. So I just gave
you those keys for Alpaca. Can you just
make sure you can actually see in the
account and that you understand the end
points and everything like that so that
you can take action in there. There we
go. So Alpaca reports your live account
with $10,000 cash and equity. There's no
positions, no open orders. And now what
else I did inside of my account here is
if I go to the um plans and features, if
we go to market data right here, we can
see that I am on a plan for 99 bucks a
month to get like real-time market
coverage and I get extra API calls per
minute and I get just more data in here.
Now, I'm not saying you have to do this
to start. When I actually did my 10K
trading challenge with Claude, I didn't
pay for this. So, it was basically just
doing research on the web and using like
secondary research in order to make the
trades. But because this one is 7 days,
I probably want more real-time market
coverage. So, paying for a subscription
like this for a month just to be able to
get better data for this challenge is
going to be important for me. But like I
said, that's not necessarily something
that you have to do. And what else is
cool is if you go to the plugins over
here and you search for something like
Alpaca or you search for stocks, there's
a bunch of other things you can connect.
So right here, you can connect Alpaca,
but this typically gives you market data
rather than letting you trade through
it, which is why we do the API key. But
there are also tons of other ones.
There's alpha stocks, there's massive,
there's stock and ETF research panel,
there's trading cursor, there's tons of
other, you know, subscriptions you can
get on or platforms that have other
types of trading data or, you know,
technical analysis that you can connect
to codecs for better research. So
anyways, now you can see that Astra came
back and said, "All of the keys work and
I do understand how I can trade and how
I can use your buying power and I can do
everything." And the next regular open
is tomorrow, September 8th, because
today is Labor Day, so markets are
closed. So now that all of this stuff
has been confirmed and we need to start
getting everything set up for tomorrow,
we have to go ahead and start building
that routine out or that scheduled task.
Now here's the one distinction about
scheduled tasks. There are two different
types. There is a local one or there is
a cloud one. And so if I come here and I
click this device, this means it runs
locally. And actually for this challenge
specifically, we are going to keep it
local. And I'll tell you why. If I go to
cloud, you can see that it says this
runs in the cloud even when the device
is offline, which is great. chat project
model and reasoning settings though are
not available and that isn't great
because specifically we want to trade
with GBT6 Astra. So I'm going to go back
to this device and now I can actually
choose the project to work inside and I
can choose the model that we want as
well as the reasoning. So I'm going to
leave this on GBD6 Astra and I'm going
to leave this on high. Now the other
thing you could do here is you could
actually have this run in the same
conversation thread every single time.
And we're actually going to do that
because that helps us set up the ability
to have you know the conversation
history be stored. And Codex has this
really nice autocompaction where I
hardly even feel like I'm in context rot
territory. So we're going to keep all of
these running together. So what I need
to do is spin up a new thread which is
going to be the trading challenge
because we're going to have to set up
what is it six different routines. And
then we're just going to point all six
of these routines at the exact same chat
to actually run in. And the cool thing
is we can actually get all this set up
with Astra and just using our natural
language instead of manually coming in
here each time. So what I'm going to do
is we're going to discard that routine
and I'm actually going to start up a new
project here. We're going to keep this
local for now. I'm going to open up the
actual folder. But first, I'm just going
to call this trading challenge. And then
we're going to open this up to the one
inside of my Herk 2 where we set up all
of those like files and things. So now
I'm in the Asha trading bot challenge.
I'm choosing that folder and I'm
creating that project right here. And
I'm just going to say, hey, I'm just
kicking off this thread. This is where
all of our actual scheduled tasks are
going to run in this one thread so that
we can keep everything consistent. So
just kicking that off so that the
routine can actually pull from it. And
I'm just going to go ahead and rename
this challenge
thread. Okay, cool. So now I'm going to
go back to the actual chat where I was
developing the strategy and I'm going to
send off the SLGO prompt to help us set
up these six routines. Hey there,
Codeex. It's time for us to now set up
the routines now that the project and
the strategy has been configured and
you're connected to Alpaca. So you
should be able to understand exactly
what to do already because we talked
about the strategy. I want you to set up
the six different scheduled tasks inside
of Codeex. They can run locally on this
device and they will each be their own
individual scheduled task. As you can
see, we've got these six different ones.
But what's important to me is that I
kicked off a thread in a new project
called trading challenge. And I kicked
off a thread and I named it challenge
thread. And I want all of these six
scheduled tasks to actually happen
inside of this thread. So you're going
to have to choose the chat when you're
setting up each of these scheduled
tasks. And that way we keep everything
consistent and um you know we have the
continuity in that way as well as the
actual progress logging and everything
that we did like that with the handoff
messages. We can just keep everything
more consistent and um I guess you know
unified by doing that. So do you have
any questions about this? Um let me know
if there's anything that's unclear and
ask me any questions and then we'll go
ahead and get everything set up. And by
the way guys, there is a way to be able
to set up cloud routines that can work
with Astra. um just not something that I
was going to dive into in this video.
But you can see now it understood what
we wanted. It found the challenge thread
and it's using that for all of the
scheduled tasks. It will return to that
same thread. So now we have these being
set up right now. And I could basically
click into here to see how they are set
up. So I can see this is the scheduled
slot number one. It's giving it all this
information. It's pointing to the right
folders and files that it needs to look
at. It's telling it what to do. If we go
to the end, we should see follow the
shared startup and end of run handoff.
save what changed, actual outcomes,
remaining risk, unresolved issues, and
the exact next job, even on a no trade
or failed run. We can see that this one
runs in the challenge thread, which is
exactly what we wanted. So, this is all
looking very good. Now, there is one
more thing that I recommend setting up
that I didn't yet instruct it to do,
which is that I obviously want to be
notified if something fails, but I also
want to be notified maybe at the end of
each day or maybe a couple times each
day, and I would like for that
notification to be sent to ClickUp. So,
that's one more thing that I'm going to
shoot off while this is actually
working. And I can click steer to inject
that message in. So I would like to have
two updates per day. I would like one
sort of like midway maybe near like the
afternoon check and then I would also
like one after market closes on you know
what happened that day and our current
position and everything like that. So if
you could just set up that automation.
So it sounds like we'll need one more
scheduled task or maybe two. They should
run in the same thread. But what I want
them to do is notify me in ClickUp. So I
want them to send me a DM. um into the
internal automations channel to ClickUp.
And so this is where you can see I when
I turned off this previous one, this one
was sending me updates over here in the
ClickUp channel and it should be doing
the exact same thing. And that way I can
just get notified right here. Now I can
see that the challenge thread is
spinning. So I wonder if it injected a
message over here. You can see this said
by chat GBT from another task. It said
the six requested Astra schedules have
been created for this exact task and
local trading challenge checkout. They
have temporarily paused during
verification blah blah blah. But this is
basically what it will look like when
the routine fires is we'll see a message
come in and it will say sent by chatbt
from another task and then we can
basically have full visibility as far as
every time messages got sent, what
happened, what Astra thought about. And
that's going to be pretty cool for us to
just have that visibility here. And of
course, we'll be able to have full
visibility inside of our actual account
as well because we can see all the
trades and all the orders and positions
and everything like that, too. You can
see that I just got a test message here
sent to my ClickUp channel. Now, this
got sent as me. It was my profile. If I
wanted to log into a different profile
like the UPAI one so that I got these
notifications in a different way, then I
could do so. But for now, this is going
to be good enough for me to be able to
get notified when something has
happened. All right, so I went ahead and
set up two extra scheduled tasks there.
1 p.m. and 3:15 p.m. Central for
notifications, and it moved the midday
report a little bit. Reports send even
when there are no trades. Test delivery
succeeded. So everything is perfect.
Everything now runs inside of the
challenge thread. So everything will be
right in here, which is going to be
great. And you can see that there's a
little clock symbol next to this thread
because it knows how all of these
routines, if I go to the scheduled and
we go to these, you can see that these
are all running and they all start
tomorrow, which is why they're currently
paused, but tomorrow they'll all be here
and active. And then we can look at
them. We can see previous runs and we
can open up the chat, which once again
takes us to the spot that they're all
going to be talking in. Now, what else
is really cool is right here, I'm on my
phone. So, this is my phone just being
mirrored onto the desktop. And if I go
over here and I click on remote, what
this allows you to do is essentially
remote into your local desktop. This is
connected to right here. So in the
challenge thread, or actually let's not
do the challenge thread. Let's just do
the develop 7-day trading strategy. And
I open this up here, I can basically
have this be perfectly synced, which
means if I come in my phone and I just
say hi, that will shoot off in my actual
desktop right here as well. So it's very
similar to the Grockpot way or the cloud
code remote. It's perfectly synced,
which means even when I'm not home, I
could come into here and open up the
challenge thread and I can always check
in on what's going on with my agents
here with the trading strategy. So, if
you didn't know about the remote, then
definitely make sure you're aware of
remote. But that really is going to do
it for this one. You guys saw exactly
how I got this set up. You saw the
strategy that we're using here. And
obviously, I'm going to be watching this
thing over the seven days to make sure
nothing is going too wrong. And if you
want to follow along and you're
interested to see how that actually
plays out with Astro, then definitely
stay tuned. That video will be coming
out in a few weeks. And if it all goes
well, I'll keep running it for multiple
months because I think it's really
interesting to see how intelligent this
stuff is truly getting and how it's able
to learn from its mistakes in the past
and change the strategy over time. But
like I said, that's going to do it. So
if you guys enjoyed, you learned
something new, please give it a like. It
helps me out a ton. And as always, I
appreciate you guys making it to the end
of the video and I'll see you all in the
next one. Thanks everyone.